snb.com 2015-03-17

# FACTS

                       WHAT DOES STERLING NATIONAL BANK DO                                             rev. June 2014
 FACTS                 WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                       Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
 Why?                  consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                       how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully
                       to understand what we do.
                       The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
 What?                 have with us. This information can include:
                               Social Security number and income
                               account balances and payment history
                               credit history and credit scores
                       When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described
                       in this notice.
                       All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
 How?                  business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                       customers’ personal information; the reasons Sterling National Bank chooses to share; and
                       whether you can limit this sharing.
  Reasons we can share your personal information               Does Sterling National             Can you limit
                                                                    Bank share?                   this sharing?
  For our everyday business purposes—
  such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                        Yes                             No
  your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
  investigations, or report to credit bureaus
  For our marketing purposes—
                                                                        Yes                             No
  to offer our products and services to you
  For joint marketing with other financial
                                                                        Yes                             No
  companies
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                        Yes                             No
  information about your transactions and experiences
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                         No                      We don’t share
  information about your creditworthiness
  For our affiliates to market to you                                    No                      We don’t share
  For nonaffiliates to market to you                                     No                      We don’t share
                         Call 855.274.2801
 Questions?
                         Representatives are available Monday through Friday, 8:30 AM to 6:00 PM
                         and on Saturday, 8:30 AM to 2:00 PM.
D-114

Page 2
 Who we are
 Who is providing this notice?     Sterling National Bank
 What we do
                                   To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and
 How does Sterling National Bank   use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These
 protect my personal information?  measures include computer safeguards and secured files and
                                   buildings.
                                   We collect your personal information, for example, when you
                                        open an account or deposit money
 How does Sterling National Bank        pay your bills or apply for a loan
 collect my personal information?       use your debit card
                                   We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                   credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
                                   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                        sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                          information about your creditworthiness
 Why can’t I limit all sharing?         affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                        sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                   State laws and individual companies may give you additional
                                   rights to limit sharing.
 Definitions
                                  Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                  financial and nonfinancial companies.
 Affiliates
                                       Our affiliates include financial companies such as Sterling
                                           Silver Title Agency, L.P. (a title insurance agency).
                                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                  financial and nonfinancial companies.
 Nonaffiliates
                                       Sterling National Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so
                                           they can market to you.
                                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                  together market financial products or services to you.
 Joint marketing                       Our joint marketing partners include companies such as
                                           credit card companies, insurance agencies and securities
                                           broker-dealers.
